Guide to the Horizons Theater Company records, 1972-2015 MS2371
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Horizons Theater Company records
1972-2015
1980-1989
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Jacobson, Leslie
MS2371
29.5 Linear Feet
Horizons: Theater from a Woman's Perspective was an award-winning theater that operated in the Washington, D.C. metropolitan area from 1977-2007. This collection contains material relating to the operations of Horizons, as well as its previous iteration, the Pro Femina Theater. The material dates from circa 1972s dating from 1980 id="aspace_88588bf8aaea3ce79eee226ce35d6b58">Materials are stored off-site, and will require additional retrieval time. Please contact the Special Collections Research Center for more information.
Arrangement
The records are organized into 6 series: Administrative materials, Correspondence, Scripts, Promotional materials, Financial documents and Productions and stage notes.
Researchers looking for a specific Pro Femina/Horizons Theatre production should consider reviewing folders containing miscellaneous materials if there is no dedicated folder(s). Some productions were not individually organized--either by the creators or during processing.
Biographical / Historical
One of the nation's oldest and longest running women's theater companies, Horizons: Theater from a Woman's Perspective was founded in 1977 as Pro Femina Theater (PFT) by Leslie Jacobson, and remained in operation until 2007. Jacobson and other Pro Femina contributors had also been members of the Washington Area Feminist Theater (WAFT), which operated from 1972-1977.
The members of PFT crafted original plays through collaboration and improvisation, exploring diverse themes including motherhood, modern romantic relationships, traditional gender roles, and aging. In 1980, the members of PFT traveled to Copenhagen, Denmark to participate in the International Festival of Women Artists and in 1981, performed in the Women's One World Festival in New York City. Within the local community, PFT hosted summer acting workshops for Washington high school students and was commissioned by the Project for Equal Education Rights (PEER) to present a play about gender disparities in mathematics education. PFT staged plays in a variety of Washington venues, including the YWCA, the New Playwrights Theater, and the Studio Theater. In 1982, PFT changed its name to Horizons: Theater from a Woman's Perspective.
From 1983-1988, Horizons was based at Grace Episcopal Church in Georgetown, DC. During their residency at Grace, the theater's productions included Signs of Life (1984), Top Girls (1985), for which Horizons received 3 Helen Hayes nominations, Miss Lulu Bett (1985), Johnny Bull (1986), Marathon '33 (1987), and Eleemosynary (1988). In 1989, a plan to relocate to a permanent space in DC's 14th Street NW Theater corridor fell through. Left without a home location, Horizons temporarily relocated to theaters across the region, including Montgomery College's Black Box Theater in Silver Spring, MD, and the Rosslyn Spectrum Theater and Gunston Arts Center, both in Arlington, VA. Through the 1990s and early 2000s, Horizons also staged plays on the campus of George Washington University.
Throughout its years in operation, Horizons premiered more than 60 original plays by national and international female playwrights and performed throughout the DC region, including at the National Archives and the U.S. Holocaust Memorial Museum. The theater also promoted community-based arts outreach, hosting playwriting and acting workshops for adults and staged readings. In May 1987, Horizons was honored with the annual Award for Excellence and Leadership in Theater by Women by the Committee for Women of the Dramatists Guild of America. That same year, Horizons performed the musical "As most successful production and for which Horizons was honored with the 1988 Helen Hayes Award for Outstanding Resident Musical. In total, Horizons productions, crew members, and actors received 22 Helen Hayes Award nominations and won 4 awards, including the Charles MacArthur Award for Outstanding New Play in 1995 for playwright Chris White's Rhythms. Horizons also created the Bravo/a Award, an annual recognition of noted Washington arts contributors that was presented from 1984-1990. Past winners included arts philanthropist Peggy Cooper Cafritz, Arena Stage co-founder Zelda Fichandler, and character actor and Horizons patron Robert Prosky.
Horizons Founder Leslie Jacobson has served as a writer, producer, director, and theater educator for more than 40 years. Before founding the Pro Femina Theater in 1977, she was a member of the Washington Area Feminist Theater, joining in 1974. Jacobson served as Artistic Director for the theater's entire tenure, also acting in and directing numerous Horizons productions. She has been nominated three times for the Helen Hayes Award for Outstanding Director of a Resident Production and was President of the League of Washington Theatres from 1985-1986. Jacobson was as a Professor of Theater at George Washington University (GW) from 1976 until her retirement in 2019. She served as Chair of the GW Department of Theater and Dance from 1995-2008. Additionally, she was Director of Graduate Studies for the Shakespeare Theater Company Academy for Classical Acting, based at GW. Professor Jacobson is a 2008 Fulbright Senior Research Fellowship recipient and graduated with an undergraduate degree in Theater from Northwestern University and a Master of Fine Arts in Directing from Boston University.
(Updated 2021)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Leslie Jacobson, 2018 [2018.004] and 2019 [2019.063].
Scope and Contents
The Horizons Theater Company Records collection contains board meeting minutes, staff contracts, subscriber lists, grant letters, correspondence, scripts, photographs, photographic slides, posters, press releases, advertisements, newspaper clippings, newsletters, programs, recorded plays, ledgers, annual financial reports, budgets, stage illustrations and diagrams, and production outlines. The material dates from circa 1972s dating from 1980
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. However, the materials found in Boxes 50 and 51 are restricted because they may contain personal or financial information. Please contact Special Collection staff for more information.
Related Materials
Related materials pertaining to Horizons Theater founder and former George Washington University Department of Theater Professor Leslie Jacobson can be found in the Theater and Dance Department records collection (RG0084), also held in the Special Collections Research Center.
Theater management; Feminism; Performing arts; Theater; Nonprofit organizations; Women -- History; Washington (D.C.)
- Administrative materials, 1977-2014; 1984-2002; MS2371 Series 1; 8.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  The materials of this series include meeting minutes of the Horizons Board of Directors, grant letters, subscriber lists, performer and staff contracts, performer biographies, theater workshop information, and staff resumes. The materials date from 1977-2014.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically in two parts due to a later addition donated in 2019 and the subsequent processing project.
  If researchers are interested in a specific production, and do not see a dedicated folder, please consider requesting folders labeled "Miscellaneous" or ones that fall within the time period of that production. A single production may have been grouped together with other materials.
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials found in Box 50 are restricted because they may contain personal or financial information. Please contact Special Collection staff for more information.
  - An Uncommon Occurrence Fall 77, 1977-1977; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mid Atlantic States Arts Consortium, 1977-1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Feminist Press Info and Fem. Theater Info, 1977-1981; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Denmark--Festival and Contacts, 1978-1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Eugene O'Neill Foundation, 1979-1979; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dramathon 79, 1979-1979; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Pro Femina, 1979-1979; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - PFT Annual Mtg 9/30/80, 1979-1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - First Draft/Second Draft Workshops, 1979-1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - It's About Time contracts, 1979-1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Theatre Space, 1979-1982; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cultural Alliance, 1979-1983; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - WETA-TV Show on the Arts "Testimony" Aug. 7, 1980, 1980-1980; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Denmark--Trip Memorabilia, 1980-1980; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Denmark--Conference Handouts, 1980-1980; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Denmark An I for A You, 1980-1980; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Postal Service Info, 1980-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board Packets, 1980-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lansburgh, 1980-1982; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bylaws/Incorp/IRS letters, 1980-1985; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Administrative - Pro Femina and Horizons, 1980-2003; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Women's One World Festival, 1981-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Resume, 1981-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Publishing - Scripts, 1981-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Women's International Theater Alliance, 1981-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Arts Newsletter from C.A., 1981-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Studio Theater, 1981-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Workshop: First Draft, 1981-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Workshops, 1981-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - YWCA: Business, 1981-1982; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Marking Time Fall '82, 1981-1983; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - NEA News NW, 1981-1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - PEER Project/Script, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - PEER, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bookings: Possibilities, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - PEER, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Jumble Sale Information, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Auditions Summer Workshop, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Direct Mail Letters - PFT and Samples, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Office Equipment Info Sign Out Sheets, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - PFT Board Minutes of Board Meetings, 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Jo Israelson Organization Study, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Meetings 9/25/82 10/19/82 Jo Israelson Moderator, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Group Process Info., 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - PFT Survey Fall '82 Notes, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Aging Show Fall 82' Planning, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Summer Youth Workshop, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Ideas for Fundraisers, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Administrative - Board Minutes, 1982-1982; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Other Performances, 1983-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Volunteer checklist to send to those interested, 1983-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Volunteer Cover Letter to Accompany 2 other sheets, 1983-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Volunteer cklist, 1983-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Pancake Breakfast, 1983-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Board Meetings, 1983-1984; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors Names and Addresses, Phone #s, 1983-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Resumes: Directors, 1983-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Royalties/Rights for Close Ties, 1983-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Close Ties Critics Mailing Addresses, 1983-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Administrative - Name Change, 1983-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Horizons (Name change and season press release), 1983-1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Church Lease, 1983-1987; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Capital Ideas, 1984-1984; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - League Minutes & Business, 1984-1984; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Board Meeting Minutes Oct., 1984-1984; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Administrative, Promo, 1984-1984; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Add Arts/Sept. 2 1:00-1:30, 1984-1984; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Horizons Goals 1984, 1984-1984; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Volunteer Advertising, 1984-1984; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Phil Fundraising Team Info, 1984-1984; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Philanthropic Society, 1984-1984; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Birth Project, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Corporate Letters, 1984-1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - NEA '87, 1984-1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Board Meeting, 1985-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Contract - Stephanie Wallis, 1985-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Mila, 1985-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Resource Organizations Women's Groups, 1985-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Interns, 1985-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bravo Tickets and Announcement, 1985-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - League of Theaters Info, 1985-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Special Events, 1985-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Administrative - Job Description and Contact Sheet, 1985-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Administrative - Budget Memo, 1985-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Volunteers/Stars/Duties Info, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Charabanc, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - This is the House, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Birthday Party Notes, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Board and Horizons Info, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Retreat, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - AU: Arts Management, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Acting Class Intro - Old, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Subscribers 86/87 Season, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Helen Hayes '86, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - National Sym. Orch - Radiothon 87 WGMS & Other Donations, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Administrative, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - CA US Air, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Veterans Organization, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Booking Contracts, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Administrative - Board Meeting Minutes, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Board Meeting, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Horizons Donation National Symphony Orchestra WGMS, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Donations '86, 1986-1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Board 86-87, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Board Resumes, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Administrative, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Subscription List 87/88, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - BD Party, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 10 years B-Day Party 87, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Wash League of Theaters, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - League of Wash Theaters Contact Sheet 1987, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - League Brochure Info '87, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Conference, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Sub Letter 87, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Cultural Alliance - Arts Wash 87-88, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Radiothon, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Kathie Collins, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Contracts 88, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Contributors 87, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Contributors 87/88, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Decade of Achievement and to dos, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Dinner and Theater Pts., 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Birthday Party 87, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Workshops 87-88, 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Info. on Kate Malin and Dorothea Malin for Ellemos., 1987-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - 87' 88 Season, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Press Releases, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - L.O.W.T.A. Minutes 87/88, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Alice - Contact Sheets for Staff, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Meyer Foundation, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - NEA 88/89, 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - TCG - Theater Comm. Group, 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - "Alice is Back" Staff Contracts, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Helen Hayes Awards 88, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Administrative - Union Codes & Contracts, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Interview w/ Leslie Jacobson - WGMS 88, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Staged Reading '88 - Eagle River, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sub Letter, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Air Exchange, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Amy McKinney, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sonja Kindley - Intern, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1988 Board Meeting minutes, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Signing Performance, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Daughter Production, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - On the Move, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter Info 88, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Play Consideration List as of 6/15/88, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Letter to Women's org, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Forum Discussion on Women Dramatists 2/88, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Three Postcards, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Bios for Three Postcards, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Patrons, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Alice Playwright Bios, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Workshop & other fliers, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 88 - Scheh - Old contact sheet, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Administrative - The Women's Project, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Thesis, "Surviving as a Small Theater Co.", 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Admin - Annual Reports, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Down Memory Lane, 1988-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Subscribers 1988-89 & Memb., 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - New American Plays Fund, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - New Space Equip., 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - League Shop Talks, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Graphic Designers, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - New Season - Spring '89, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Concierge, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - DCAAH Sal Asst '89, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 88-89 Memberships, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - NEA Grant 89-90, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - AT&T Grant, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - NPT Lease, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Space 87-88, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Bio for Craig Lucas, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - League of Washington Theatres, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 3P Ushers, 1989-1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - American Express Grant, 1989-1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - P.R. Shop talks - League of Wash, 1989-1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - LOWT Calendar of Events, 1989-1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Boeing Grant, 1989-1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Riggs Bank, 1989-1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Woolly Mammoth Meetings, 1989-1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Pump boys mailing invite list, 1989-1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Meyer Proposal, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cafritz Grant 89-90, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Coonley Ferry Foundation, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - USAir, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - What's Going On, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Bd. Mtg. Minutes 1989, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Congress House of Representatives, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Board Current, 1989-1999; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper #2 "On the Horizon", 1990-1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Feminist Theatre, 1990-1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Reckless, 1990-1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Alice Press Release - Bio Composer, 1990-1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Six Women with Brain Death, 1990-1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Pepco Auditorium, 1990-1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Administrative - Construction Delay Memo, 1990-1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Contracts, 1990-1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - C&P Grant, 1990-1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper - 3rd Addition, 1990-1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Reckless - Press Night/Concierge Reception/VIP Reception, 1990-1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Reckless - Timetable/Contact Sheet/Schedule, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Horizons, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Box Office - LGS, 1993-2000; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Arlington County, 1994-1998; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Administrative - Grants, Notes, Memos, 1995-2004; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Administrative - Board Mins., Budgets, 1996-1997; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Leslie, 1996-1997; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Planning, 1997-1997; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Rebirthday Party, 1997-1997; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Arl. Co. Info, 1997-1997; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Subs 97-98, 1997-1998; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Cultural Alliance, 1997-1999; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Board Potential Members, 1997-1999; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Board Meetings, etc., 1998-1999; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Subscriber list 98-99, 1998-1999; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Subscribers 99-00 2000-01, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - League of D.C. Theatres, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Material handed out @ BOD Meeting Feb. 00, 2000; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Contact Sheets, 2000; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - New Script Ideas, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Intern from A.U., undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Performance Contracts, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Biographical Notes: Board, Staff, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Old Staff & Company List, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Complimentary Ticket Policy, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Resumes - Marking Time, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Actors' Resumes, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Summer Workshop It's Our Turn: Script Draft, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Summer Workshop Comment Sheets, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - PIE Light Loan Agreement Women's Work, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Working Calendar, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Beth Joselow, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Marketing Task Force, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Scene Study Workshops, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Hard of Hearing Proposal Notes, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Advisory Committee, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Bd. Bios/Letter, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Space, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Agenda - Horizons, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 22)